我最爱的美女好啊
There is my favorite girl!
我好激动可以周末一起去做水疗哦
I'm so excited about our SPA weekend!
我也是
Oh, me too.
如果你们到了那边还记得的话
If you think of it while you're there,
我的防晒粉马上就不够用了
I'm dangerously low on sunscreen powder.
粉
Powder?
等十年后 你的脸变成老苹果的时候
You know, you won't be smirking 10 years from now
你就笑不出来了
when your face looks like an old apple.
我首次得到出任普里契特橱柜CEO的奖励
I just got my first perk as C.E.O. Of Pritchett's Closets.
我承包的水疗馆项目完成了
I finished a big job for a spa,
他们为了感谢我
and as a thank-you,
给了我两个免费水疗周末的名额
they sent me a free weekend for two.
但菲尔太怕痒了 不能接受按摩
Phil's too ticklish for massages, though.
可我不会
But I am not!
我听说好多明星都去那里
I heard it's the place where all the stars go
往脸上倒热泥巴
to get hot mud poured into their faces.
我只是等不及要看这位的素颜了
I just can't wait to see this one without makeup.
如果你看到了 那将是你死前见到的最后画面
You do, it will be the last thing that you will ever see.
我还记得我第一次获得的工作奖励
I remember my first big perk for a job well-done.
我给《家有阿福》的主创升级了柜子
I had upgraded some closets for guy who created "ALF".
六周以后 我看节目里
And six weeks later, I'm watching the show.
阿福狂骂的一个帅哥邮递员
There's ALF sassing this handsome mailman
就叫杰·普里契特
named Jay Pritchett.
我还录下来了呢
I still got it on Betamax.
我记得 我们第一次约会时你就给我看过
I remember. You showed it to me on our first date.
杰 准备好一起去看拳击比赛了吗
Jay, you ready to watch the, uh, fight together?
好啊
Yep.
就我们两个
Just two of us.
我本来把今天晚上都计划好了
I had the perfect night planned --
我一个人 付费观看拳击比赛
alone, pay-per-view boxing --
爱尔兰的骄傲[酒]对战古巴的轰动[雪茄]
The pride of Ireland versus a Cuban sensation.
在拳击场里 也在我的血液里
In the ring and in my bloodstream.
结果歌洛莉亚和米奇尔掺和进来了
Then Gloria and Mitchell got involved.
杰 小卡也要看拳击赛
Jay, Cam is gonna watch the fight, too.
你们何不一起看呢
Why don't you two watch it together?
太好了 不然小卡只能一个人去酒吧看了
Oh, good, because Cam was just gonna watch from a bar by himself.
我好喜欢 简直像你们俩来了场约会
I love it. It's gonna be like you have a date!
我不知道怎么回事 但每次我和杰独处
I don't know what it is, but Jay gets uncomfortable
他都会觉得不自在
when it's just the two of us.
然后害我也觉得不自在
And then I get uncomfortable,
总感觉有必要说点什么
and I feel like I have to say something.
完美
Perfect.
今天是希特勒的生日
Today's Hitler's birthday.
米奇尔 我们走了
Mitchell, we're going!
菲尔人呢 电影院里的座位肯定坐满了
Where is Phil? The theater's gonna be packed.
亲爱的 你的书呆子朋友在等你
Honey, your nerd friend is waiting.
谁敢召唤我的大名
Who dare invoke my name?
撤退信号来了
That's my cue.
是我 你的毁灭者
It is I, your destroyer!
莉莉 你确定不跟我们一起去看电影吗
Lily, you sure you don't want to go to the movies with us?
最后问你一次哦
Last chance.
讲什么的来着
What is it about again?
《无限的守护者们》讲述的是
The Defenders of Infinity are heroes
从几个不同时间流来的英雄
from several different time streams
一不小心进入了未来 但却不知道...
that make their way into the future without --
并不是真的未来
Um, it's not really the future
因为时间流都是共存的
since the streams have always coexisted.
不要这样 别把我当成"脑叶人"
Don't do that. Don't treat me like I'm a lobotomorph.
莉莉 你不会想去的
Lily, you don't want to go.
你将会是全影院唯一的女孩
You'll be the only girl in the theater.
好了 你们该走了
All right, you guys should head out.
我们很想走了
We would love to.
不用担心
Oh, and don't worry.
莉莉的保姆把今晚计划得满满的
Lily's babysitters have a big night planned --
拼图 乒乓球 桌游
puzzles, ping-pong, board games.
现在还是"让曼尼赢吧 不然他该哭了"计划吗
Are we still in that "Let Manny win or he cries" Phase?
不是
No.
我们该走了 我们要不要通过不同时间流走
We should get going. Are we taking separate time streams?
当然 如果我们想昨天到达的话
Sure, if we want to get there yesterday.
这一盆绿苹果 可真让人放松
Ah, there's something so relaxing about a bowl of green apples.
我已经把烦恼都忘掉了
I already forgot all my problems.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
-什么 -就是啊
- What? - Exactly.
我们在所有抽屉上都用了静音滑道
We used WhisperQuiet gliders in all the drawers.
减少了不少"柜噪"
Oh, really cuts down on C.N.
那是我们这行的术语 意思是"柜子噪音"
It's industry jargon for "Closet noise."
这个降噪技术能用到人身上吗
Does that technology work on people, too?
你说得对 我保证不会再三句话不离本行了
You're right. I promise -- No more shop talk.
是谁啊
What is this?
家里的烟雾警报响了
Our smoke alarm went off at home.
我相信不是什么大事
I'm sure it's nothing,
还是给卢克打个电话确认一下吧
but I'm still gonna call Luke just in case.
直接转到语音信箱了
And it's straight to voicemail.
曼尼 我们看到烟雾警报响了
Hello, Manny. We saw that the smoke alarm went off.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
天啊 卢克的留言信息是
Oh, God. Luke's outgoing message
又长又稍稍有点性别歧视的说唱
is a long and vaguely sexist rap.
好的 宝贝 保持优秀
Okay, Papi. Stay perfect!
一切都好
Everything is okay.
他们在烤饼干呢 结果烤糊了一批
They were baking cookies and they burned a batch.
好吧
All right.
不过我们家烤箱明明是坏的
Except our oven isn't working.
曼尼从来不撒谎的 不如这样吧
Manny would never lie. You know what?
我打电话叫个俄国按摩师
I am gonna call for a Russian masseuse.
他们的手非常有劲儿 都是拧衣服练出来的
Their hands are very strong from wringing laundry.
你考虑一下
Think about it.
他们当时急着赶我们出家门
They were very eager to get us out of the house.
他们肯定有什么阴谋
They're up to something.
你疑心太重了
You are too suspicious.
你太轻信别人了
And you are too trusting!
今年卢克已经被警察抓过
Luke's already been arrested this year.
几周前 他喝啤酒还被我们撞见
A few weeks ago, we caught him with beer.
我刚刚的说唱都比他好
Even that's a better rap.
我听到卢克的名字好几次 却没提过曼尼
I'm hearing a lot of Luke's name and none of Manny.
你觉得曼尼不会趁你不注意的时候
You don't think Manny's up to the same things
也在一起搞鬼吗
when you're not paying attention?
你疯了 曼尼讨厌啤酒
You're crazy. Manny hates beer.
那就是果香博若莱红葡萄酒
A fruity Beaujolais then.
你想干嘛就干嘛
You can do whatever you want.
我去看看我家孩子
I'm gonna go check on my kid.
我好讨厌这些滑道 都没法摔出点气势
I hate how good those gliders are!
我好兴奋 感觉自己像个小少年
I am so excited. I feel like a teenager.
我也是 但是作为古人托尔夫的我
Me too. Although, as Torf the Ancient,
已经从巨星爆炸到七月联盟中
I have seen everything from the Great Star Explosion
阅尽世间万物了
to the Seven Moon Alliance.
克莱尔说对了 没有姑娘
Claire was right. No girls.
菲尔
Phil?
詹姆斯
James!
你好呀
What's up?
我去年卖给这位酷哥一栋山间小屋
I sold this cool cat a house in the hills last year.
从那以后 他的青草地乡村乐队就飞黄腾达了
Since then, his bluegrass band has really taken off.
特别疯狂 我们开始是想讽刺才搞乐队
It's so crazy. We started doing it ironically,
结果不知不觉的 竟然真的做起来了
and before we knew it, we were actually doing it for real.
90年代的时候 我也经历过
That happened to me in the '90s
想说"抱歉" 结果真被"抱"了
with saying, "Exsqueeze me."
从你的古人托尔夫造型
Well, I assume from your Torf the Ancient costume,
-和你的苍白奴隶造型中看出来 -我这不是造型
- and your pale slave getup... - Not a costume.
你们是来看《无限的守护者们》的
hat you guys are here to see "Defenders of Infinity."
没错
Oh, yeah!
超级好看
Oh, it is so incredible!
-真的吗 -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
对了 你们想感受彻底震撼的话
Hey, if you really want to be blown away,
我这有两颗特质小熊软糖可以给你们吃
I've got two special gummy bears you can have.
我们一人就一颗吗
Just one for each of us?
相信我 一颗就够了
Believe me. One is all you need.
我们可以去小卖部再买点
I guess we can get more at the concession stand.
不 他们可不卖这种橡皮糖
No, they don't sell gummy bears like these here.
你是从欧洲带回来特别酷的对吧
You get extra cool ones from Europe or something.
你们怎么还没明白 这是大麻
Guys, how are you not getting this? It's pot.
我也不知道为什么 反正我从来没抽过大麻
I don't know why, but I've never tried marijuana.
对 我也没有
No. No, me neither.
总有些什么事阻拦我
Th-There was always something stopping me --
比如要照顾莉莉啦
needing to take care of Lily,
花样滑冰荣誉准则啦
the figure-skating honor code,
不想吸得神志不清 在高中意外出柜啦
not wanting to accidentally tell everyone in high school I was gay.
从来没人递给我抽过 挺奇怪的
People never offered it to me, which is weird
因为在大学里我也算是有头有脸的人物
because in college, I was kind of a big man on campus.
我建立了一个大型组织
I founded a major organization --
全国负责任的拉拉队员协会
the National Association of Responsible Cheerleaders.
-缩写是NARCs[缉毒署] -是啊
- Uh, NARCs. - Yeah.
来 这个要45分钟才起效
Here. They take 45 minutes to hit,
现在就吃
so take them now,
等电影开始 你们的状态就刚刚好
and you'll be good to go when the movie starts.
好
Okay.
如果我们想尝试这个
Um, you know, if -- if we ever were gonna try this,
今晚也算是个完美时机
tonight's kind of the perfect opportunity.
我觉得你说得对
I guess you're right.
不用带孩子 穿的是尼龙扣运动鞋
No kids. I'm wearing Velcro sneakers.
要吗
Should we?
我一直都想知道那是什么感觉
I've always wanted to know what it would be like.
再说了 我今天去了健身房
Plus, I went to the gym today.
我理应尝点甜头
I deserve a sweet.
-那就来吧 -好
- Let's do it. - Okay.
我在发抖 谢谢你
I'm shaking. Thank you.
-干杯 -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheersies.
慢点嚼
Chew smaller.
好啊
'Sup?
我的天
Oh, my God.
不敢相信我们居然真吃了 太刺激了
I cannot believe we're doing this. This is so exciting.
天啊 我就知道犯了个大错
Oh, God. I knew this was a horrible mistake.
我收到一个警报 烟雾警报器被触发了
I just got an alert. Our smoke alarm when off!
吐不出来
It's not coming up.
没事
Okay, okay.
放松 我现在打给卢克
Relax. I'm gonna -- I'm gonna call Luke,
-看看怎么回事 -好
- find out what's up. - Yeah.
转进语音信箱了
Voicemail.
不过这段说唱还挺搞笑的
This rap's hilarious, though.
-打给克莱尔 -她不在家
-Call Claire. -She's not home.
我们得回去看看
We're gonna have to check this out.
不 拜托 这种警报一般都没什么事
No, come on. Those alerts are always nothing.
再说了 我们的犯罪事实
Plus... our crime.
听着 我们的座位是有号的
Listen, we have assigned seats
这个也要45分钟才起效
and 45 minutes till this kicks in.
我们完全有时间打车回家
That gives us plenty of time to Uber home,
确保一切安好
make sure everything's fine,
平复下我的心情 然后再回来
touch up my veins, and get back.
我设个闹钟 这样就知道什么时候起效
I'll set an alarm so we know exactly when it hits.
你说得对 莉莉也在呢 我们走吧
No, you're right. Lily's there. Yes, yes. Let's go.
再说了 我们不会想等到飘飘欲仙的时候
Plus, we're not gonna want to deal with this
再来处理这种事的
when we're high and paranoid.
天啊
Oh, God.
你觉得到飘飘欲仙的状况会很严重吗
Do you think the paranoia will be bad?
你的衣柜生意如何
So, how's the closet business?
-我两个月前退休了 -对哦 对哦
- I retired two months ago. - Right. Right.
我下个月打算清洗一下地毯
Uh, getting our carpets cleaned next month.
拜托 简直荒谬
Oh, come on. That's ridiculous.
赫南德兹绝对轻松拿下这场比赛
Hernandez has this fight in the bag.
是啊 简直是易如反掌
Yeah, it's gonna be such a cakewalk.
根本就不该给他钱
He shouldn't even be getting paid for it.
这些人简直胡扯
Can you believe these guys?
无意冒犯 可就算奥布莱恩有那么半点清醒
No disrespect, but if O'Brien's even halfway sober,
都能把赫南德兹撕碎
he takes Hernandez apart.
对 他臂展更长 出拳更猛
Yeah, he's got a better reach, better jab,
脚步之灵活迅速堪比踢踏舞
and I haven't seen feet that fast since Riverdance.
你们看起来还挺自信
You guys seem pretty confident.
要不小小地赌个十美元如何
Uh, care to make a friendly $10 bet?
我们应战 简直是这辈子挣的最轻松的钱
We'll take it. Easiest money I ever made.
你们简直疯了 奥布莱恩是个废物
You're crazy. O'Brien is a mook.
赫南德兹就是个半吊子
Well, Hernandez is a palooka.
我宁愿是个半吊子也不愿意是个废物
I'd rather be a palooka than a mook.
两个傻屌也好意思说这种话
Well, that's a lot of talk coming from a couple jabronis.
小卡 淡定 我们这是说着玩呢
Cam, calm down. We're just having fun here.
不是吧 那个词已经很过分了吗
Really? That's -- That's the line?
怎么回事
What happened?
该死 奥布莱恩把他击倒了
Damn it! O'Brien knocked him out!
这么快 我们完全错过了
Already? We missed the whole thing!
厨房很忙
We're backed up in the kitchen.
抱歉了 你们点的餐还要再等会
Sorry, guys. Your food's gonna be a while.
我想过要走
I thought about leaving,
可我不想让杰不高兴
but I didn't want to make Jay feel bad.
我在等一个三明治
I had a sandwich coming.
我就说吧 屁事都没有
I told you. Nothing!
我觉得像这么平静无事有点不正常
A little too much nothing, if you ask me.
你们怎么回来了
What are you guys doing here?
我忘了带拖鞋
I forgot my slippers.
酒店不是会有拖鞋吗
Doesn't the hotel have slippers?
我来问问题
I'll be asking the questions.
你们怎么可能把巧克力饼干烤糊
How did you manage to burn chocolate-chip cookies
烤箱明明都坏掉了
in an oven that doesn't work?
曼尼的意思是煎饼
Oh, Manny meant pancakes.
我们在做巧克力煎饼
We're making chocolate-chip pancakes.
瞧吧 我们走吧
You see? Now, let's go.
这会应该有按摩师往我身上撒盐才对
Somebody named Olga should be salting me like a pretzel!
没什么事吧
Is everything okay?
没事 警报误响了
Oh, yes. It was just a false alarm.
那我们就回电影院去了
Well, then we should probably get back to the theater.
开映前的趣味问题
Those pre-movie trivia questions
还等着我们去回答呢
aren't gonna answer themselves, are they?
-其实是自问自答 -等一下
- Actually, they do. - Wait a minute!
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on...
这个东西
here, huh?
我闻到廉价啤酒味 有人在开派对
I smell cheap beer. Someone's been having a party.
克莱尔 你这是在发疯
Claire, you're just being crazy.
你看一看周围 根本就没事
Take a look around! Nothing is going on!
没有什么派对
There is no party!
所有人都淡定
Everyone just be cool!
看过那个独臂高尔夫球员的故事吗
See that story about the one-armed golfer?
没有
No.
就是 有这么个人...
Yeah, well, it's this guy and he's...
就这样了 他是个独臂高尔夫球员
Well, I guess that's it. He's -- He's a one-armed golfer.
厨房到底是有多忙
How backed up is that kitchen?!
这两个家伙
These guys!
嘿 你们两个小鬼 过来
Hey, you rascals. Get over here.
我们正准备走
We're on our way out.
别急 你们不想找机会把钱赢回来吗
No! Don't you want a chance to win your money back?
每人5块钱而已 无所谓了
It's 5 bucks each. We're good.
别啊 来吧
No! Come on!
会很好玩的
It'll be fun.
老兄 你把我胳膊抓痛了
Dude, you're hurting my arm.
来一局桌上足球 要么赢回去要么输双倍
No, a game of foosball, double or nothing.
-我不想... -说定了 走吧
- I don't think -- - You're on! Let's go!
菲尔 我们还有多长时间
Phil, uh, how long do we have?
17分钟
17 minutes.
我们是指距离电影开始的时间
Till the movie, is what we're talking about.
我们就是两个看电影的人
We're just two guys seeing a movie.
在把事情搞清楚前 任何人都不准离开
No one's leaving here until we get to the bottom of this.
我的天 来个人给我按背
Oh, my God. Somebody give me a back rub!
曼尼 卢克 都过来
Manny! Luke! Get in here!
你们去搜查房子 看看有什么可疑之处
You guys go search the house. Find something suspicious.
这会不会跟塞洗碗机一样
Is this gonna be like loading the dishwasher?
我先塞了一次 然后你又重新塞了一次
First I load it, then you reload it?
如果你亲自...
Wouldn't it be faster if you actually...
菲尔 快去
Phil, go!
什么事这么重要
What's so important?
我在坐等我的肖像画呢
I'm sitting for my portrait.
少来这套 我知道你俩开了个派对
Oh, knock it off. I know you two threw a party.
我不开[扔]派对的 克莱尔
I don't "throw" a party, Claire.
是真的 他什么东西都扔不动
It's true. He can't throw anything.
而且如果我真的举办了派对
And if I were hosting an event,
我要把冰雕藏哪
where did I put the ice sculpture?
把餐前点心藏哪
Where did I stash the hors d'oeuvres?
把爵士三人乐队藏哪
Where did I hide the jazz trio?
问得好
Good question,
因为你连"独奏"的[啤酒]都藏不好
considering you couldn't even hide... the Solo.
文字游戏玩得不错 妈
Nice wordplay, Mom,
但那个杯子已经放那三天了
but that cup's been there for like three days.
我之前什么都没说
I didn't want to say anything
因为我以为那是你用过的
'cause I thought it was yours.
没错 那方法很大胆
Yeah. It was bold.
可楼上那些孩子不会一直保持安静
But those kids upstairs weren't gonna stay quiet forever.
只要一个人手机没电 就会有人说话
I was one dead phone battery away from a conversation breaking out.
当然了 开派对是很冒险
Sure, throwing a party was a risk,
可我们学校刚来了两个超辣的交换留学生
but two hot exchange students just started at our school.
最妙的就是 她们还不知道
Best part is, they don't understand
我们到底有多不酷
just how uncool we are.
暂时而已
Yet.
于是 我们在走廊里走着
So, we were walking down the hallway
然后在储物柜旁停了下来
when we stopped by the locker --
"披萨日"
Ohh, pizza day.
那是我们的私人教练
That's our personal trainer.
他不喜欢我们吃糖类食物
He hates it when we eat carbs.
我们的机遇期很短
We had a short window.
我们必须尽快给她们留下好印象
We needed to impress them fast.
所以我们就用无限的汽水贿赂莉莉
So, we bribed Lily with all the soda she could drink
开了这场派对
and threw a party.
开始一切都很顺利 直到有人触发了火警
It was going great until someone set off the alarm
因为他非要抽那个傻帽烟斗
because he just had to smoke his dorky pipe.
傻帽
Dorky?
是啊 休·海夫纳抽烟斗就"泡不到"妞呢
Yeah, because Hugh Hefner doesn't get girls.
我也爱你 妈妈
I love you, too, Mommy.
没事了 朋友们
All clear, party people!
我告诉她我们在烤饼干
I told her we were baking cookies.
老兄 我家的烤箱坏了
Dude, our oven's broken.
我妈绝对会起疑心来查岗的
My mom's definitely gonna get suspicious and check on us.
那说明我妈也会来
That means my mom's coming, too.
我让大家快撤
I'll get everyone to leave,
你来处理啤酒和你的大餐
you get rid of the beer and your idea of a spread.
等等 我们不能放弃
Wait. We're not giving up yet.
啤酒乒乓球比赛才刚开始
The beer pong tournament just started,
姑娘们为我们讲的笑话笑个不停
the girls are laughing at all of our jokes,
还以为我们跟汤米·卡特西那种家伙是朋友
and they think we're friends with guys like Tommy Cutahee.
派对真棒 路易斯
Great party, Lewis.
谢了 汤米
Thanks, Tommy.
从现在开始 我叫路易斯
From now on, I'm Lewis.
如果不采取行动 我们会被抓到的
We're going to get caught if we do nothing.
要是我们把大家都藏起来
What if we hide everyone long enough
直到我妈检查完走了呢
for my mom to check on us and then leave?
这么做可不值
It's not worth it.
两位 我们什么时候玩《天堂七小时》
Guys, when do we play Seven Hours in Heaven?
派对转移到楼上啦 朋友们
Moving the party upstairs, people!
好了 这里没人
Okay. No one's here.
是你手表闹钟响了吗
Is that your watch alarm?
我们得走了
We have to get out of here!
我可不想在克莱尔面前进入嗑高的状态
I do not want to be high in front of Claire!
等等
Wait.
我想我有感觉了
I think I'm feeling something.
不要啊
Oh, no.
你感觉怎么样
What are you feeling?
很好
Nice.
天啊
Oh, God.
你有感觉了吗
Are you feeling anything?
没有
No.
那你怎么歪着站
Then why are you leaning like that?
我没歪啊
I'm not leaning.
也许是你站歪了 所以看着我是歪的
Maybe you're leaning so it looks like I'm leaning.
是啊 你说得对
Oh, yeah. You're right.
菲尔 你在干什么呢
Phil, what are you doing?
还在搜
Still searching!
有什么可疑的吗
Anything suspicious?
说"没有"[别说话]
Say nothing.
好的
Okay.
菲尔
Phil?
回答她啊
Answer her!
你刚刚叫我别说话
You said "Say nothing."
-我是让你说"没有" -那个词
- I mean say the word "Nothing." - Word.
没有
Nothing!
-说的好棒 -谢谢 兄弟
- That was so good. - Thanks, man.
好了 菲利普 集中精神
Okay, Phillip. Focus.
我们得快点搜完这所房子
We have to finish searching this house
以免待会儿表现得诡异或是...
before we start acting weird or...
没有
Nothing!
说得好棒
That was so great.
当然 名师出高徒嘛
Yeah, I learned from the best.
来吧 你这个混蛋 进球啊 混账
Come on, you jerk. Get in there, you son of a bitch!
对了 宝贝 就这样
Oh, yeah, baby. Here we go.
昨晚我搞你妹的时候
That's what your sister said last night
她就是这么说的
when I was banging her.
什么 该死的 维克
What?! Aw, damn it, Vic!
小卡搞了维克的妹妹
Cam was banging Vic's sister.
太经典了
Classic!
快点吧
Oh, just hit it already.
昨晚小卡搞你妹的时候 她也是这么对他说的
That's what your sister said to Cam last night when he was banging her.
我说得好笑吗
Did I do it?
你真的好棒
You're so good!
好棒
Yes!
曼尼 曼尼 曼尼
Manny, Manny...Manny.
怎么会这样呢
How did we get here?
你是个好孩子
You're a good kid.
你跟这事一点关系都没有
You didn't have anything to do with this.
只是在错误的时间出现在错误的地点
You were in the wrong place at the wrong time.
我说的对吗
Am I right?
但是某人必须为这事接受惩罚
But someone's going down for this.
你觉得会是那个白人小孩吗
You think it'll be the white kid?
克莱尔
Claire!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我正在努力挖出真相
I am trying to get to the truth.
搞清家里到底发生什么的唯一办法
The only way I'm gonna find out what really happened here
就是让那两个熊孩子互相揭发
is to get those two clowns to turn on each other.
家里什么事都没有
Nothing happened here!
就算真的有
And even if it had,
曼尼也不会出卖他最好的朋友
Manny's not gonna rat out his best friend!
我想我要乖乖跟她合作了
I think I'm gonna take the deal.
不行
No!
你要是认怂 我们跟交换留学生
You cave, we don't stand a chance
就没机会了
with those exchange students.
那些姑娘看不上弱爆的
Those girls don't respect weak, little nerds
害怕妈咪惩罚的小书呆子
afraid of being punished by their mommies.
她们经历过战争
They've lived through wars.
她们是从葡萄牙来的
They're from Portugal!
我听见有动静
I heard something.
你听见了吗
Did you hear something?
没
No.
我现在在尖叫吗
Am I screaming right now?
没有
No.
保持镇定 我们就快离开这了
Stay cool. We're almost out of here.
这没人
All clear.
我们检查下卢克的房间
Let's just check Luke's room.
然后就可以告诉克莱尔我们什么都没发现
Then we can tell Claire we didn't find anything.
好吧 我们有两个办法
Okay, there's two ways we can play this.
好的
Okay.
好吧 如果我们告诉克莱尔这些孩子的事
Okay, if we tell Claire about those kids,
那就得留在这儿惩罚曼尼
we're gonna have to stay here and punish Manny
以及 那个谁
and the, uh -- the other one.
那可不妙
That's no good!
我觉得那样就瞒不住我们的罪过了
I don't think we can hide our crime!
如果我们不告诉她呢
Well, then what if we don't tell her?
那样我们就成了坏家长吗
Does -- Does that make us bad parents?
或者说我们是坏家长
Or are we bad parents,
是因为我们自己都嗑嗨了 却还要惩罚孩子们
because we're punishing our kids while we are high?
无论哪样 我们都坏得透透的
We're bad parents either way!
真是个噩梦
This is a nightmare.
-你们好啊 -你好 小蛋糕
- Oh, hey, guys. - Hey, cupcake!
我刚是叫她"小蛋糕"吗
Do I call her "Cupcake"?
别担心 我来化解尴尬
Don't worry, I'll make it normal.
怎么了 小蛋糕
What's going on, cupcake?
你俩还好吗
Are you guys okay?
好 好 好的很 怎么会不好
Yeah. Yeah, we're okay. Why wouldn't we be okay?
小蛋糕
Cupcake.
我当时醉得一塌糊涂 以为他俩嗑高了
I was so drunk, I thought they were stoned.
卢克 卢克 卢克
Luke...Luke...Luke.
保守秘密是很不好受的
Keeping a secret like this is tough --
会吞噬掉一个人的灵魂
eats away at a man's soul.
妈妈 我只有一个问题
Mom, I have one question --
你为什么憎恨自己
Why do you hate yourself?
什么
What?
你晚上本可以尽情地享受高级奢华的按摩
You have one night in a spa to be massaged and pampered,
但你却情愿留在这
but you're here.
你为什么觉得自己不配得到快乐
Why don't you think you deserve happiness?
这是我今天想深入解决的谜团
That's the mystery I'm interested in solving today.
什么声音
What is that?
那是派对的声音 歌洛莉亚 对吧
That is the sound of a party, Gloria, huh?
曼尼
Ay, Manny!
明天我和我妈去上母子曼波舞课一定尴尬到爆
Tomorrow's gonna be one awkward mother/son mambo class.
接下来 我要打你老娘的屁股
Next up, I paddle your mother.
-爸爸 -克莱尔
- Dad. - Claire!
嘿 这才是我真正的女儿
Hey, this is my actual daughter.
今晚好几次提到了你
You came up a few times tonight.
我"老婆"也是
So has my "wife."
你们在这搞什么鬼
What are you doing here?
我们在酒吧 游戏都玩遍了
We ran out of games to bet on at the bar.
克莱尔 有些事我们得告诉你
Claire...there's something we have to tell you.
我们决定做什么来着
What did we decide to do again?
我们...
We, uh...
我们...我们要组织下语言
We're g-- We're gonna need a minute.
我告诉过你 孩子们没犯事
I told you there was nothing going on with the boys.
你说得对
You're right.
孩子们 我道歉
Boys, I apologize.
我们以人格担保 没有任何可疑情况
We can confirm that there's nothing suspicious anywhere.
很抱歉砸坏了你的桌子 路易斯
Sorry about your table, Lewis.
我还要赶另一个派对
I have another party.
我就知道
Oh, I knew it!
我就知道这俩小子在密谋着什么
I knew these two were up to something.
现在你要怎么为你的"妈宝"曼尼辩护
What do you think about your precious Manny now, huh?
我相信一定是卢克的主意
I am sure it was Luke's idea!
但先别急着放弃他
But do not give up on him yet.
我知道山上面有个营地
I know that there is a camp up in the mountains
专门收容这种坏小孩
where you can send bad kids.
不 我也是共犯
No, it was my idea, too.
是我触发烟雾报警器的
I'm the one who set off the smoke alarm.
是我用汽水贿赂莉莉的
I'm the one who bribed Lily with soda.
是我在洗衣房放了一个红色电灯泡
I'm the one who put a red light bulb in the laundry room
来营造性感的气氛
to give it a sexy vibe.
你不能再固执地认为我还是你的乖宝宝
You've got to stop thinking of me as your perfect little boy.
亲爱的
Honey.
-楼上有个派对 -楼上有派对
- There's a party upstairs. - Party upstairs.
我真不敢相信我家宝贝竟然对我撒谎了
I cannot believe that my baby lied to me.
我真不敢相信我家宝贝坦然受贿
I cannot believe my baby accepted a bribe.
要是我就会将关注点放在
I'd be more concerned with how natural she is
-她浑然天成的喝酒姿势 -够了
- with that bottle in her hands. - Okay.
我真不该太相信自己的孩子
I shouldn't trust my kid so much.
我应该像克莱尔那样 不信任任何人
I have to be more like Claire and not trust anybody.
我也不希望我猜对了 但事实如此
I didn't want to be right, but I am.
于是就这结果了
So here we are.
至少我们还有艾丽克斯
At least we still have Alex.
你们连一个好孩子都没培养出来
You guys don't have any good kids,
所以现在谁是坏家长
so who's the bad parent now, huh?
-谁都不是 -菲尔 别说
- Nobody. - Phil, no, don't.
不 我来处理
No, no. I got this.
克莱尔 我知道为什么你一直担心
Claire, I know why you're always worried.
因为你不知道未来会发生什么
Because you don't know what's going to happen.
那叫"未知恐惧"
It's called fear of the future,
或"未恐" 或"未惧"
or "Fof" Or "Fotf."
但容我剧透下 一切都会好得很
But spoiler alert -- It's gonna be great.
大家 我有俩字要告诉你们
Guys, I have two words for you --
想想"时间旅行"
think about time travel.
如果你们能够穿越回到从前
If you could go forward in time and turn around
转身看到此时此景 我们会说
and look at this moment, we would say,
"真是太棒了"
"This is all super chill."
我们的孩子们都是好人
Our kids are good people.
他们长大了很优秀
They turn out great.
-菲尔是对的 -真的吗
- Phil's right. - Really?
那...那我也有一些想说的
Oh, t-then here's something, too.
我小的时候 我从没想过我还会在这儿
When I was younger, I never thought I would be here.
但现在我就在这
And here I am.
这是什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
老天
Oh, God.
听着 你不用紧张
Look, you got to relax.
他们不会有事的
They're going to be fine.
人们都有出人意料的一面
People have a way of surprising you.
没错 我们今晚也有难忘的美好经历
Yes, you see, we had our own journey tonight --
原本不搭调的两人一起玩得很开心
an unlikely duo thrust together.
没轮到你发言 小卡
Not your moment, Cam.
好吧 我会给你们发群邮的
Oh, right. I'll send a group e-mail.
亲爱的 别担心
Honey, don't worry.
你作为家长 远胜过当年的我和迪迪
You're better parents than Dede and I ever were,
你长大了也依然很棒啊
and you turned out all right.
谢谢 爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
我们现在该怎么办
But what do we do now?
我们该放过这些孩子们一马吗
Are we just supposed to let these kids off the hook
因为我们曾经也和他们一样顽劣
because we were as bad as they are?
不 我们要当伪君子
No. We'll be hypocrites.
跟所有家长一样
Like all parents!
卢克 曼尼
Luke! Manny!
都给我滚过来
Get your asses in here!
还有 只有我一个人看出来
Also, am I the only one that sees
这两个蠢货嗑药嗑得飘飘欲仙了吗
that these two idiots are high as kites?
米奇尔
Mitchell?
天哪 她还在跑
Oh, my God. She is still going.
她到底喝了多少汽水
How much soda did she have?
当你和米奇尔刚在一起时
You know, when you and Mitchell first got together,
你经常约我一起参与很多活动
you used to ask me to do a lot of stuff.
我当时才刚刚加入你们的家庭 而且
I was new to the family, and I --
我非常想博你欢心
I really wanted you to like me.
但我总是太急切 太情感外露
But I always seemed to be too much, too demonstrative,
太小题大做 所以我收手了
too dramatic... so I stopped.
今晚我玩的很开心
Well, I had fun tonight.
我不介意你继续时不时地
I wouldn't mind if you still
追在我屁股后面讨好我
chased me a little bit sometimes.
杰 来抱一个
Oh, Jay. Get in here.
有点太快了吧
It's going too fast.
我很抱歉 一步步来
I'm -- I'm sorry. Baby steps.
不是 那个跑步机快得都能让她上天了
No, the treadmill's about to launch her through the drywall.
莉莉
Lily.